<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Barbie Calculator</string>
    <string name="heading">Bella\'s Enchanting Secret</string>
    <string name="paragraph">In the world of dolls, a special Barbie named Bella lived in a magical dollhouse with her friends. But Bella had a secret - every night, under the glowing moon, she came to life! With sparkling eyes and a wide smile, she ventured beyond her dollhouse, spreading joy wherever she went.\n\n

Her nighttime escapades were her cherished secret, a chance to explore the wonders beyond. Bella loved watching children play during the day but yearned to roam freely.\n\n

One night, while exploring the toy store, she met Twinkle, a mischievous little elf. They became inseparable, dancing under moonlight, singing to the stars, and making memories to treasure.\n\n

Bella learned the true meaning of friendship and discovered a heart filled with love and kindness. One special night, she made a wish on a shooting star, asking to bring joy to children everywhere.\n\n

To her delight, her wish came true! Every morning, Bella woke up with newfound magic. Children who held her felt warmth and comfort, carrying a piece of her enchantment.\n\n

The legend of Bella, the magical Barbie, spread far and wide. Children cherished her as a friend who brought happiness into their lives. Bella\'s secret had become a beautiful reality, making the world a little brighter, all thanks to her heart full of magic and love.</string>
    <string name="button_back">Back</string>
    <string name="barbie_background">Barbie background</string>
    <string name="Clear">c</string>
    <string name="division">Division</string>
    <string name="Multiply">*</string>
    <string name="multiply_description">Multiply</string>
    <string name="backspace">Backspace</string>
    <string name="btn_7">7</string>
    <string name="btn_8">8</string>
    <string name="btn_9">9</string>
    <string name="subtraction">Subtraction</string>
    <string name="btn_4">4</string>
    <string name="btn_5">5</string>
    <string name="btn_6">6</string>
    <string name="addition">Addition</string>
    <string name="btn_1">1</string>
    <string name="btn_2">2</string>
    <string name="btn_3">3</string>
    <string name="heart">Heart</string>
    <string name="btn_0">0</string>
    <string name="Dot">.</string>
    <string name="animation_heart">Animation heart</string>
    <string name="equal">Equal</string>
</resources>